

I'm a result and a process-oriented person with a strong theoretical background and good practical experience in Web development. Thorough and precise in everything I do, have a keen interest in technology, mobile applications and UX.

## SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3, SASS/SCSS, BEM, Bootstrap
- JS(ES5, ES6), jQuery
- React/Redux/React hooks
- Git, npm
- Gulp
- Photoshop, Figma

# **PORTFOLIO**

- https://olegobiukh.github.io/eco-cosmetics/
- https://olegobiukh.github.io/kickstarter/
- https://olegobiukh.github.io/layout\_miami/
- https://olegobiukh.github.io/layout\_dia/
- https://olegobiukh.github.io/portfolio2019/
- https://olegobiukh.github.io/react-sw/

# OLEG OBIUKH

FRONTEND REACT DEVELOPER

## CONTACTS

• PHONE: (099) 531-3954

• TELEGRAM: @olegobiukh

• GMAIL: oleg.obiukh@outlook.com

• GITHUB: https://github.com/olegobiukh

• SKYPE: oleq.obiuh

 linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/oleg-obiukh-237362139/

## EXPERIENCE

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

INVESTORS IN IDEAS | NOV2019 - PRESENT

- Tech stack: React, Redux, SASS, Git
- Duties: Working with a Front-End part of Marketplace, regular communication with Back-End team.
- Achievements: Started to work autonomously in less than a month.

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

FLEPRON | MAY 2019 - OCT 2019

- Tech stack: Bootstrap, JS, Angular.js, jQuery, Jira
- Duties: Developing and support admin Websites (creating admin panels and platforms for displaying data and statistics was my primary duty), communication with the team (English), testing and searching for bugs.

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

TRAINING PROJECTS | DEC 2018 - MAY 2019

- Tech stack: HTML5/CSS3, JS, React
- See my code examples at github.com/olegobiukh

# **EDUCATION**

Design, Manufacture and Maintenance of Radio Equipment

College of Computer Technology and Economics, Kyiv